♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Ah, homecoming games are
so exciting.
It's like Friday Night Lights
and I'm Connie Britton.
Wrong, and nope.
God, I wish I was the coach
in the locker room
giving an inspiring speech
to the players.
Gonna tell you the one thing
every football player
needs to know--
"When you kill yourself,
don't touch the brain
'cause they got to take it out
and look at it."
[all] Yeah!
Oh, no, it's Gayle--
the PTA president
whose passive-aggression
can drain your life force.
Hi, Lois Griffin.
So, you did know
there was a game?
Oh, hi, Gayle. Yeah, I knew.
I'll take
those cupcakes you made.
[gasps] Oh, you don't seem
to have any to donate.
No, I didn't have the time.
You have three kids,
I totally get it.
I have four, and I work.
Sometimes it's hard
to read a short email.
-Spam folder?
-Oh, spam folder, yes.
I don't have that problem
because most of us
got rid of AOL years ago.
If you'll excuse me,
I have to go find my husband,
who makes $220,000 a year.
[groaning echoes]
[video game cheering]
Welcome to the Adam West
High School homecoming game.
If anyone is here
to shoot the place up,
please do it
after the halftime show.
The girls have worked very hard.
But first, join me
as we say goodbye
to Adam West High's longest
serving teacher, Mr. Trampledon.
He's retiring after 50 years,
and is known these days
as the last teacher in school
to employ a paddle
and/or closed fist
on misbehaving students.
He was formally asked
to stop doing that last week
and... decided just to retire.
And he'd better step lively or--
-[grunts]
-[team whooping]
And... tonight's game
is dedicated
to the memory of Mr. Trampledon.
And now, give it up for
our Homecoming King and Queen.
They're off to never leave town
and slowly decay
before our eyes.
Next up,
crowning our Homecoming Dunce,
Chris Griffin!
[announcer] This is
Chris Griffin's fourth win
for Adam West High
Homecoming Dunce,
even though he's only
a sophomore.
[sighs] Four years in a row is
nothing to be proud of.
Dynasty.
[TV announcer]
We now return to Hulu's
Pam and Tommy. Lee Jones.
Baby, are you gonna steer
the boat with your penis?
Why would I engage
in such foolishness?
How you feeling
after yesterday, Chris?
Terrible. Every year
I'm the Homecoming Dunce,
and every year
the bullying gets worse.
Hello, everyone.
I have some news.
I got an email
from the school saying
they're looking
for a substitute teacher
to replace Mr. Trampledon,
and... I applied.
And they accepted.
-What?
-Seriously?
I don't know if that's
"mute the TV" news.
Mom, you can't!
Don't you need
a master's degree to teach?
A master's degree is needed,
and I told them I had one.
You lied?
I manifested success.
I'm a woman in her 40s,
so I manifest.
Lying is just me taking
action steps over the truth.
The corpse of the truth.
You can't just say
you're a teacher.
Oh, no? Every other man
these days throws on a dress
and suddenly he's a woman, so...
Okay, I met
with community leaders,
and I'm going
to learn and listen.
Anyway, I'm a teacher now.
You saw how unpopular
I am at school.
Having my mother as a teacher
will make things worse.
I thought about that, Chris,
which is why I applied under
the name Lois Pewterschmidt.
But you've taught
at Adam West before.
People won't fall for it.
Oh, maybe I'll wear
a blonde wig?
[gasps] Might even add
a sexy beauty mark
so I look like Marilyn Monroe.
Or Cindy Crawford?
Or Eva Mendes?
Or Gabriel Macht?
The guy from Suits?
That won't work.
I don't want this.
-I'm going to Bonnie's room!
-You mean your room?
No, Bonnie's room.
[applause on TV]
Yeah, first Wednesday
of every month,
Bonnie visits her mom
in the home.
Oh.
You know,
when she and I do this,
the first person to solve
the final puzzle on Wheel
doesn't have to pay
for the pizza.
Yeah, well, uh,
Bonnie's not here.
Glad to have you aboard,
Miss Pewterschmidt.
Let's show you around.
There's our BLM banner.
That should probably come down,
I think we're
all done with that.
And our trophy case.
We don't have many,
so I've filled it out
with other items of achievement.
-Oh, is that you and--?
-Counting Crows, yes.
If you have an Amex Platinum,
you can use points
and get backstage
at select concerts.
You have an Amex Platinum?
Nah, I was tenth caller
on the radio.
No yearly fees
on a fast dialing finger.
Life hack!
Students, here's your new
substitute teacher,
Miss Pewterschmidt.
Hello, people.
What a nice group of young,
fresh, unknown faces.
Whoa! Check it out.
A blonde.
Ha, that means
she starts at a B-minus.
Look at that body.
Today I'm learning numbers--
36-24-36.
Oh! I want to know
when this went
from history class
to "wood" shop.
[purrs] Oh, doing
too much physical stuff.
Oh, my God.
They're all leering at my mom.
This is more embarrassing
than when Dad
ruined my birthday party.
Dad, is it almost time
for the piñata?
Dad?
Chris! I think I screwed up
the party job assignments.
Ow! Damn it.
I'm not full of candy,
I'm a guy!
-[cheering]
-Ooh, I am full of candy.
Wait a minute,
if I'm full of candy,
where are my insides?
I did it. I'm alive!
Now to move in with my sister,
Hilaria Baldwin.
♪ ♪
[phone buzzes]
Oh, no! Cinematic text messages
give everything away.
[Trey] So, Griffin,
what's your problem?
-What did you say?
-What?
-I said, "What did you say?"
This might go easier
if you just let me sit
at the cool kids' table.
[indistinct chatter]
Wow, I can't believe
I'm at the cool kids' table.
Hi, I'm Cody.
Uh, here's some bread
to start you off,
and I'll be back in a moment
to take your orders.
Wow! Are those parmesan crisps?
You can have
the pumpernickel stick.
Oh, that's the only thing
I don't want.
So, why were you weird
with Miss Pewterschmidt?
We're teens.
We're horny for everything.
If something's not totally
repulsive, it's hot.
Don't you think she's hot?
Yeah, I guess
she's a total hottie.
What would you do with her?
Like, if you went home
with her tonight.
We'd eat dinner, talk a bit.
And then go upstairs
and straight to bed.
There you go.
Now you're talking.
Guys, a table just
opened up on the terrace.
-Oh, perfect.
-Oh, no, we'll get that.
[quiet chatter]
[sighs] I didn't even
need the sweater.
So Miss P., huh?
I tell ya, I'd jump up
her poodle skirt
and say I'm the dog catcher.
[school bell rings]
Man, it's like nobody
can see or hear me.
Things have been weird
ever since me and Frenchy were
drag racing for pink slips and--
[magic chiming]
Wait a minute.
Am I dead?
-Yes, you are.
-You can see me?
I can see all the dead.
It is my gift... and my curse.
Hey, Meg, the, uh, ghost toilet
is clogged again.
Requires a human fist.
[sighs]
Quick, Chris, get in.
[gasps] You see what I see?
Griffin's getting in the car
with Miss Pewterschmidt!
Aw, he works fast, dude.
Quick, Chris, get down.
Whoa!
Griffin's a selfless lover.
It's so great he's having sex.
[rock music playing]
♪ Guy friends gettin' horny ♪
♪ About their guy friends
having sex. ♪
[announcer]
There's nothing wrong with it.
I'm beginning to think
this whole teaching thing
is a lot easier
than they let on.
Kids, when you're
bagging groceries,
do you ever wonder who invented
the shopping bag?
-[student] Margaret Knight?
-It was Margaret--
You saw it on the board!
Griffin, we saw you driving away
with Miss Pewterschmidt
yesterday.
Did you score? If you closed
the deal with a teacher,
you'll be a legend forever.
Well, let's just say,
she and I slept.
Together.
Under the same roof.
-All right!
-Of course, we had dinner first.
There you go.
And then I ate
her Outback Steakhouse salad,
-which she didn't want.
-As someone who only listens
to the first half
of sentences, nice.
-She single?
-No, she's married.
Her husband was there all night.
I think they live together
more as brother and sister
than husband and wife.
Oh, happens to
a lot of couples, I hear.
There's a bit more going on.
I don't think there's a lot
of dew left on his lily, right?
You know what, Griffin?
We're gonna carry you out
on our shoulders because of sex.
All right, just be careful.
-[cheering]
-Easy. I'm husky.
Falling six feet for me
is like nine feet for others.
I don't feel supported!
Well, Chris Griffin.
Uh, hello, Miss Pewterschmidt.
I'm so proud of you.
I know you didn't want me
to be your teacher,
but it's such a thrill
to see you making new friends.
See you later, Chris Griffin.
Hey, stud. The cheerleading
squad decorated your locker.
We do that for all the boys
who "score."
Wow. You guys decorated
my locker?
Well, the male cheerleaders did.
We decorated it in what is known
as the Hollywood Regency Style.
A delightful blend of Art Deco
themes and silhouettes.
Did you notice the pop of color?
The pop of color was my idea.
Hey, I heard
a weird rumor about you.
Oh, that I took
a trip to Jamaica
and my room was
robbed of everything
except my camera and toothbrush?
And then I carried on
using my toothbrush,
as one does on vacation,
but when I got home,
I developed my film
and there was a picture
of a Jamaican man using
my Oral-B as his anal-B?
Yeah, it sort of happened,
but I was the Jamaican man.
No, people are saying
you're sleeping
with "Miss Pewterschmidt,"
who is Mom.
You do know she's Mom, right?
I know she's Mom.
And I may have said some things
that made people think
we're having sex.
But the guys in class
now think I'm cool.
Chris, Mom could get arrested.
Mom knew when she took this job
there was a chance
we'd wind up pretend-banging.
I'm not going back
to being unpopular.
Well, Chris, tell me just
one thing about Mom...
is she bigger than me?
[announcer]
This program is now "TV-MA"
because of what Meg just said.
Got to say, I'm pretty beat.
[groans] Sleeping
with Miss Pewterschmidt,
but we're not sleeping,
you know?
Hard to sleep
when you're doing stuff.
Yeah.
But what did you do, exactly?
Well, she has this whole
"mom" thing going on.
Last night, she scolded me
for tracking mud
in the living room.
Obviously trying to get me
out of my shoes.
Ooh, what a turn-on.
That's not sex.
Tell us exactly
what sex you and she did.
[gulps] Come on, Chris.
You've seen thousands
of hours of porn.
You can do this.
Well, Miss Pewterschmidt was
a braless real estate agent
who was showing me a large,
mostly empty home
in Van Nuys, California,
and she'd do anything
to make the sale.
I showed her a thick wad of ones
and we were off to the races
on a brown leather couch
next to an empty CD tower.
That's just porn.
Yeah, you're just making
this whole thing up.
No, we really had sex.
I mean, the house purchase
fell through, though,
because of some issues
with the appraisal,
but that's not uncommon
in this market.
We want a picture.
A naked picture of Miss P.
or you're a liar.
A naked picture? Okay.
But I have to warn you,
sometimes she looks exactly
like Halle Berry
bent over the sofa
in Monster's Ball.
Get us a naked picture of her.
And until then, go sit
with the angry hearing aid kids.
♪ ♪
Oh, look who it is. Mr. Popular.
Oh, look who it is.
Mr. Popular.
Oh, hear who it is.
Okay, Chris, you can do this.
Plenty of people have taken
nude pictures of their mom.
Possibly Liz Hurley's
weirdly pretty son
with whom she seems
entirely too close.
♪ ♪
I can't. I can't.
It's my mom.
I'm not a dirtbag.
Psst. Chris.
That it has even gone this far
means you are a dirtbag.
Own it.
I don't know, Mr. Quagmire.
"In order to find
real happiness,
"you must learn to love yourself
for the totality
of who you are."
Portia de Rossi.
[phone beeps]
[camera clicks]
Where's the picture, Griffin?
Awesome. Send it to us.
Promise you won't share it?
Of course not.
We're best pals.
Well, we have made
a lot of memories together.
♪ So take the photographs
and still frames in your mind ♪
♪ Hang it on a shelf
in good health and good time ♪
♪ Tattoos of memories
and dead skin on trial ♪
♪ For what it's worth,
it was worth all the while ♪
♪ It's something unpredictable ♪
♪ But in the end is right ♪
♪ I hope you had
the time of your life. ♪
Okay, I was thinking
of the wrong stuff,
but I guess
I can trust these guys.
[phones chiming]
[phones chiming rapidly]
[phone chimes]
"Miss Pewterschmidt
is sleeping with a student.
Here's the proof."
That's her.
And it looks like someone
in her home is using
"Kerasilk Shampoo
for color-treated hair."
I wonder who?
I'll never tell.
Kerasilk Color Shampoo.
It keeps color-treated
hair vibrant,
and that keeps me
out of the salon.
Principal Shepherd sounded mad
when he called me in
this morning.
Well, his ex-wife's now
garnishing his sandwiches,
and I don't mean adding parsley.
-[bell dings]
-You can go in now.
[sighs] He must have found out
about the master's degree.
Okay, I'll go in
and I'll just be honest.
Miss Pewterschmidt,
I have a very grave matter
to discuss with you.
And I know what it is.
I'm guilty.
Well, I appreciate the honesty.
I mean, I did the same thing
at my son's preschool
-and no one cared.
-Wha--?
I just want to touch kids,
and I have.
All of them.
Even the girls.
One boy was unhappy with his D
and I promised
to help him get it up.
Then it was, "Cram, cram, cram."
I'm close to breaking
my pencil in outrage.
One boy's a little slow,
but I whisper in his ear,
"You can do it,"
and the smile on his face
when he finishes.
Miss Pewterschmidt,
you cannot sleep with students!
What? No, never!
I thought you were talking
about me lying
about having a master's degree.
Oh, no, no, no.
Take a look at my master's
on the wall there.
"The Harvard Yale
Principal School
of the Republic of Cuervo."
We all lie.
Who's gonna pay for a master's
to teach
at the high school level?
But still, how did a student
get this nude photo of you?
Oh, my!
Okay, I don't hate that angle.
But I-- I think I know
who took this.
I'll take care of it.
And-and can you send me
the photo, please?
[phone chimes]
Can you delete it
from your phone?
Of course. Click.
-All you did was say, "Click."
-It's an old phone.
Hear you're doing it
with a teacher, huh?
I'm proud of you.
They say her husband's got
no more dew on the lily.
Christopher Cross Griffin!
How could you?
Oh. Hi, Mom.
Peter, your son told everyone
that he and I were
sleeping together,
and then, then he sent
a nude photo of me
to his friends and now
it's all over school.
The soap acts like a bikini,
hiding everything.
There's a subreddit for that.
Let me see if it's there yet.
I'm sorry. I didn't think
it would get around.
[computer starts]
Chris, if people think
I'm sleeping with a student,
I could go to jail.
Now, you are gonna march
into school tomorrow
and tell everyone the truth.
I just wanted to be in with
the cool kids no matter what.
I saw popularity
and I went for it.
Oh, honey, you wanted
something and you lied.
You were manifesting.
I wouldn't use
that awful term, but yes.
You made it. "Soapkinis."
Lot of upvotes.
You know, Chris,
I bet your new friends
will admire your honesty.
You're brutally naive.
You're also on the subreddits
"Over40GoneWild,"
"Mombod," and you're even
the alluring photo
that gets me to click on a link
about celebrity bankruptcies.
[gasps] Joey Lawrence
sold his condo at a loss?
Come on, let's go out and get
some ice cream, my little man.
"Floyd Mayweather Jr.
KO'd by the IRS"?
I don't know, Mom.
People may talk.
Not ready to laugh
at this, Chris.
Sheena Easton lives
in reduced circumstances
in Henderson, Nevada? No!
Good morning, everyone.
I've done something terrible,
although not as terrible
as the cafeteria meatloaf.
Thought I'd open
with a little humor.
Ha! Popular kids are
always funny.
Chris, get to the point.
Well, I told many of you
that I was sleeping
with Miss Pewterschmidt.
I shared a shower photo of her.
If you haven't seen it yet,
it's on the subreddit
"Soapkinis."
You're the man, Chris!
No, I'm a liar.
None of that happened.
Mo-- I mean, Miss Pewterschmidt,
is an excellent teacher
who would never do such a thing.
I hope everyone can forgive me
and see that I just wanted
a few friends.
-[coughs] Loser.
-[coughs] Liar.
[coughs]
Real cough, long COVID.
♪ ♪
Now, hold on, hold on.
Let me tell you all the truth.
Chris Griffin was
the biggest thing I ever had.
[all gasp]
Oh, I thought
I was gonna break in two.
He was 22 inches and 11 pounds.
But I knew he was gonna
change my life for the better.
[cheering]
[Chris] Mom got six years
for sex with a minor.
Asher died
in an e-bike accident.
And as for me,
I married Liz Hurley's
strangely attractive son.
My name is Chris Griffin Hurley.
I took his name.